[Music]
most filipinos worry worry for the kids
their future their homes where they
might regret not living life to the
fullest
because of that really because of that
they don't get to enjoy their lives and
just end up getting by
now what if what if what if those
worries were gone and that they all went
away because of people like us
like you like you like you like you that
is fwd don't get me wrong fwd still is
an insurance company
but we're not your ordinary insurance
company insurance
isn't only about money though there's a
lot of money here i'll give you that
because
insurance at least for us is for having
the guts having the courage
we live in the moment to live in the now
by securing your future
by protecting what's important flying
biking skydiving scuba diving rock
climbing you're covered no catch
insurance is as much about tomorrow as
it is about today
today today insurance is just about
commissions hate that thinking insurance
is for
the mission to make people people people
get ready
ready ready ready to live that is fwd
as financial wealth planners you may not
be designing cars building the next big
high rise or painting the opus of this
generation but
as financial wealth planners you make
them all of them possible
heroes to the everyday heroes that's who
you are with
fwt helping filipinos secure their
future fulfill their dreams while
fulfilling yours
at your own pace at your own place no
exaggerations doesn't matter how much
you've got right now
because you don't need capital doesn't
matter who you are why castle
from the world of finance retail realty
pharma or even fashion you are meant to
be here at fwd doesn't matter if you're
new or already in the world of insurance
there's always room to grow and succeed
with us our training tools and support
in a category of its own here you'll
find what it takes to lead to innovate
transform to really be successful as
successful as you want to be
growth only happens in a place that
keeps on moving forward
meaning where growth truly begins at fwd
so join us because you're meant to live
to thrive
not just survive join us because we get
people and we put them at the center of
everything we do appeal because we are
fresh relevant and authentic juan young
chantia
woman because going paperless visa
forest won't suffer for your success
because the future is digital
and digital is fwd join us trips in new
york
geneva north pole talina because there's
no greater heroism than bringing out the
hero in everyone
join us so you can change the way people
feel about
insurance we are the philippines we are
asia we
are fwd